http://www.kinspeed.com/privacy/

Skip to contentPrivacyPrivacy and Cookie PolicyPrivacy and Cookie PolicyKinspeed Ltd are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This privacy policy explains how we will use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?We collect information about you when you register with us or place and order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions and register for events. Website usage information is collected using cookies.HOW WILL WE USE THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU?We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to email you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website.Kinspeed Ltd will not share your information for marketing purposes with other third-party companies. In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from, credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.MARKETINGWe would like to send you information about our products and services which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please email data-controller@kinspeed.com or write to us at the contact address below.ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND CORRECTIONYou have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email data-controller@kinspeed.com or write to us at the contact address below.We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.COOKIESCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.orgYou can set your browser to not accept cookies and the above websites will tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.RETENTIONWe retain your information you provide to create your account for as long as you hold an account with us.Personal information used to provide products and services to you will be kept long enough to provide you with the product support and service.We may retain some usage statistics (including IP addresses) for as long as we have a business purpose to improve our site but these statistics are not linked to deleted accounts.OTHER WEBSITESOur website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website, so when you visit another website via one of these links you should read their own privacy policies.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYWe keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. This privacy policy was last updated on 24/05/2018.HOW TO CONTACT USPlease contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:By email: data-controller@kinspeed.comWrite to us: Kinspeed Ltd, Privacy Team, Albion House, Ravenshorn Way, Renishaw, Sheffield, S21 3WYThis website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
100% Free Whitepaper: Six Key Strategies To Grow Your Profits Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper revealing six key strategies to grow your profits.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: NetSuite And The Inc. 5000 Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: Addressing The Challenges Of A Growing Biotech CompanyPlease enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: NetSuite For Electronic Manufacturers Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: Giving The Contract Furniture Industry The Technology It Needs to Thrive Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: How Technology Drives Success In The Promotional Products Industry Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: The Value Of A True Cloud ERP Platform for Food And Beverage Companies Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: The Buyer's Guide to Financial Management Software Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: Enterprising Moves For Cloud ERP Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
100% Free Whitepaper: The Case For A Continuous Close Please enter your contact details to receive your free whitepaper.
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Company (required)
×
